interacnetwork.com 2012-12-11

# Privacy - Interac - Teach with Japan's leading provider of ALTs

This Privacy Policy is intended to inform you about what type of information and how such information is collected on the Interacnetwork.com site and our practices with respect to that information. These guidelines apply only to the Interacnetwork.com site (herein referred to as the “Website”). If you register as a member of the Website or  apply for a position with Interac through the “Website”, you will need to provide certain personally identifiable information (otherwise known as (PII), including your name, e-mail address, age, mailing address, city, state and zip code and passport information. You will also need to supply a username and password. If you do not provide the requested information you will not able to register as a member or complete your application for a position.

**What Interac does**

Interac presents materials on the Website exclusively for viewing by prospective employees to get a better sense of our company and work in Japan. Interac reserves the right to change how we handle the information we collect and process through the Website at any time. We will update this Privacy Policy to reflect any changes and such changes will take place immediately thereafter.

**What type of information we collect and how we use it**

Our web server automatically recognizes, collects and/or stores information such as the visitor's IP address/Domain name combination and any referring sites for each visitor to the Website. Unless you provide PII to Interac via links to email contacts provided on the Website or by accessing any system linked to it, we will collect only anonymous and aggregate information .There are several ways that we may collect such information. For example, we may use technologies known as cookies and web beacons. “Cookies” are small text files that identify and store certain information on your computer. We may use cookies to, among other things, monitor Website usage, customize Website features and identify your computer’s operating system and browser. Most browsers will allow you to erase cookies from your computer hard drive, block acceptance of cookies, or receive a warning before a cookie is stored. Interac may also itself use, or engage third parties to use, eb beacons and other similar technologies for researching certain usage and activities on our Website. Again, the information collected by Interac or requested from third parties through these eb beacons is in an aggregate, non-individually identifiable form and is used to find out more about users including demographic information and usage patterns for more accurate reporting and to improve the effectiveness of our marketing and recruiting activities. We may also use, or engage third parties to use, pixel tags or other technology to research or track your usage activities with respect to e-mails from us.

**How does Interac collect PII?**

Interac may ask you to provide PII meaning individually identifiable information such as your e-mail address and name to enable you to receive our newsletter and updated job information. Also, you will be asked to provide PII through any application through any system linked to the Website. Interac may combine the information you provide on our Website with information we may collect offline from you or from third parties to better process your information and possible application to us.If you do not want us to have your PII, do not submit PII to the Website

Interac will not share any of your personal information with any third party except (i) to employees of other companies within the Selnate Group and certain independent contractors and independent contractor companies who supply services to Interac. These companies include Selnate USA, Selnate, Selnate Publishing, Maxceed and Selti (ii) as may be required by a court order (iii) to certain appropriate parties such as law enforcement or other government agencies, in connection with a criminal investigation or other legal action if Interac believes it is necessary to protect the company, its clients or the general public

To change or update the personal information you have provided to Interac, please visit Your Profile web page and click on the appropriate tab for the information you wish to revise or update.

**How we store information**

Interac takes reasonable steps consistent with industry standards to ensure that any PII collected from you through the Website is secured from loss, alteration, unauthorized access, or destruction or leak while in storage under our control. However, Interac does not guarantee that unauthorized access will never occur.

**Our policies regarding children**

Interac will not knowingly collect PII from anyone under the age of thirteen (13) years of age.

**Consent to processing**

By providing any personal information, all persons, fully understand and unambiguously consent to the collection and processing of such information in their own country and in Japan

**Questions**

If you have any questions or comments about our personal information practices or about this Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact us.
